A Guide to the Richmond Renaissance Inc. Archives, 1956-1995
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series II--Riverfront, n.d. 1983-1991
  - Buy a Block in Downtown Richmond-Ground breaking/kickoff 1986 (Box 8)
  - Buy a Block in Downtown Richmond-Jaycees and General Promotion Information 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Buy a Block in Downtown Richmond-Lawler-Ballard Advertising 1986 (Box 8)
  - Buy a Block in Downtown Richmond-Sales 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  - Canal Walk-Dedication-Brochures, Correspondence, Notes 1987 (Box 8)
  - Condition and Dimension Survey Railroad Pin Trusses to Belle Island, Richmond, Virginia-Whitman, Reguardt and Associates 1988 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence 1982-1988 (Box 8)
  - DRC Consultants-Nils Olsson-Contract 1986 (Box 8)
  - DRC Consultants-Nils Olsson-Contract Negotiation Correspondence 1986 (Box 8)
  - Feasibility Study: Vehicular Access Bridge South Bank of James River to Belle Isle-Whitman, Requardt and Associates 1988 (Box 8)
  - Fundraising 1986 (Box 8)
  - Fundraising-Corporate 1985 (Box 8)
  - Fundraising-Grass Roots 1985 (Box 8)
  - Fundraising-Grass Roots Group, n.d. 1985 (Box 8)
  - Fundraising-Notes, Correspondence, Donor Lists, n.d. 1984-1987 (Box 8)
  - James River Discovery Program-Cash Flow Analysis, Contributions 1986 (Box 9)
  - James River Discovery Program-Contributions form Corporations 1984-1987 (Box 9)
  - James River Discovery Program-Foundation Grant Applications-Correspondence, Notes 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - James River Discovery Program-Fundraising Status Report 1984-1986 (Box 9)
  - James River Discovery Program-Ground Breaking Ceremonies July 2, 1986 (Box 9)
  - James River Discovery Program-Notes, Procedures 1986 (Box 9)
  - James River Discovery Program-Riverfront Modest Improvement Plan 1985 (Box 9)
  - James River Discovery Program-State Funding 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Kanawha Canal Feasibility Study 1988-1990 (Box 9)
  - Lee Bridge-Notes, Correspondence 1985 (Box 9)
  - Market Analysis, n.d. 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - Notebook and Catalog, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Old Lee Bridge, n.d. 1984-1987 (Box 9)
  - Parking Lot Design Contract-Whitman, Reqardt and Associates 1986-1991 (Box 9)
  - Parking Lot-Tredegar Street Correspondence, Drawings, Miscellaneous, n.d. 1986-1991 (Box 9)
  - Parking Lot-Tredegar Street Correspondence, Drawings, Miscellaneous, n.d. 1991 (Box 9)
  - Planning-Includes Richmond Riverfront Concept Plan by EDAW, Inc. 1989 (Box 9)
  - Public Relations; Slide scripts, Newspaper Clippings, n.d. 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Riverfront-Budget Analysis, n.d. 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Riverfront-Budgets, n.d. 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Riverfront-Committee 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Riverfront-Cost Models, n.d. 1983 (Box 9)
  - Riverfront-Improvements Working Group 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Riverfront-Status Meetings 1985 (Box 9)
- Series III--Sixth Street Marketplace 1956-1986
  - 6th and Marshall Parking Garage 1984 (Box 10)
  - 600 E. Broad St. Office Building/WCA 1984 (Box 10)
  - Marketing Plan 1986 (Box 10)
  - Action Committee-Correspondence, Report 1983 (Box 10)
  - Affirmative Action and Minority and Tenant Opportunity 1984 (Box 10)
  - Allied/Miller and Rhoads-Financial Commitments to Sixth Street Marketplace 1983-1984 (Box 10)
  - Allied/Richmond Renaissance/Enterprise Development Co. meeting May 30, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Appraised value of Sixth Street Marketplace 1984 (Box 10)
  - Architecht-Miscellaneous Correspondence, Reports (1 of 2) 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Architecht-Miscellaneous Correspondence, Reports (2 of 2) 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Bank Commitments 1983-1984 (Box 10)
  - Bank Loan Documents 1984 (Box 10)
  - Baskervill and Son (Box 10)
  - Blue Law Issue 1984 (Box 10)
  - Blue Laws-Public Relations Institute 1983, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Blues Armory 1984 (Box 10)
  - Blues Armory-Historic Design; Tax Credit, Dept. of Interior-Correspondence, (Including Sen. John Warner and Historic Richmond Foundation) Architectural Drawings, Notes 1984 (Box 10)
  - Blues Armory Utility Bills 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Bridge Design and Costs-Correspondence, notes 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Budget 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Building Code Fire Protection/Building Specifications-The Whiting Turner Contracting Co. 1984 (Box 10)
  - Bus/Stops/TIAA/CREF 1984 (Box 10)
  - Cash Flow-Chronology 1983 (Box 10)
  - Cash Flow, n.d. 1984 (Box 10)
  - City Council 1983 (Box 10)
  - City of Richmond-Correspondence, Notes 1984 (Box 10)
  - City of Richmond-Minority Business and Tenant Opportunity Program 1984 (Box 10)
  - City Ordinances (Box 10)
  - City Plans-Project One 1983 (Box 10)
  - Community Development Block Grant Predevelopment Contract (Box 11)
  - Community Development Block Grant 1981-1984 (Box 11)
  - Conflict of Interest 1984 (Box 11)
  - Construction Letter, n.d. (Box 11)
  - Construction Scheduling 1984 (Box 11)
  - Construction-Tax Issues 1984 (Box 11)
  - Consultants-Advertising, Graphic Arts, Architecture, n.d. 1984 (Box 11)
  - Cost-Budget 1984 (Box 11)
  - Council of Organization-Correspondence, Minutes 1984 (Box 11)
  - Council of Organizations-Correspondence, Notes, Minutes, Members List, Misc. 1983-1985 (Box 11)
  - Council of Organizations-Design Review-Correspondence, Notes, Minutes 1984 (Box 11)
  - Council of Organizations-Liaison Committee Meeting-Correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - Council of Organizations-Meeting November 14, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Council of Organizations-Minutes 1985 (Box 11)
  - Council of Organizations-Parking Strike Force 1985 (Box 11)
  - Crystal Palace (Letter to Mrs. Mary Tyeler Cheek) 1984 (Box 11)
  - Davis-Bacon-Correspondence, Notes, n.d. 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Davis-Bacon Wage Dispute 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Debursement Schedules-Allocation of Costs 1984 (Box 11)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development 1984 (Box 11)
  - Department of Planning and Human Development-Correspondence 1984 (Box 11)
  - Department Stores-108 Reporting 1984 (Box 11)
  - Department Stores-Proposed Agreements 1984 (Box 11)
  - Design-Correspondence, Notes, Programs, Schedule 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - Development Budget 1983 (Box 11)
  - Disposition Development Agreement-City of Richmond, Festival Diogenes Corp. Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority, Richmond Renaissance Inc. and Richmond Festival Marketplace 1984 (Box 11)
  - Distribution Lists 1984 (Box 11)
  - Downtown Office of Promotion (Box 11)
  - EEO Plan 1983 (Box 11)
  - Enterprise Development Company-Correspondence 1982-1984 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Development Company-Correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Development Company-Correspondence, Notes 1986 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Development Company-Correspondence, Reports, n.d. 1982-1984 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Development Company-Feasibility Study 1983 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Development Company-Feasibility Study [Includes Drawing of Proposed Marketplace] 1983 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Development Company-Proposal and Expectations 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Foundation 1983 (Box 12)
  - Enterprise Study Group 1984 (Box 12)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment-Correspondence, Notes 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment Plane-Correspondence, News Clippings 1983 (Box 12)
  - Equity Syndication-Correspondence, Reports, n.d. 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Festival Diogenes Corporation 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Festival Marketing Openings-Waterside (Box 12)
  - Festival Marketplace Briefing April 8, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Fifth Street Parking Deck 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Finance and Marketing-Correspondence 1984 (Box 12)
  - Finance Committee 1983 (Box 12)
  - Financial and Economic Benefits-Report 1983 (Box 12)
  - Financing Alternatives for Syndication 1984 (Box 12)
  - Financing Banks 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Financing-Capitol Fund Drive 1984 (Box 12)
  - Financing-General 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Green Advertechs, Inc. 1983 (Box 12)
  - Grand Openings/Post Opening Calendar 1985 (Box 12)
  - Ground breaking 1984 (Box 12)
  - Guarantee Agreement-City of Richmond, Richmond Festival Marketplace Partnership, Enterprise Development Co. 1984 (Box 12)
  - Hotel Hiring, n.d. (Box 13)
  - HUD Executed Grant Agreement September 24, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Ideas for Opening [promotional shopping bag-Pavilion at the Old Post Office, Wash. D.C.] (Box 13)
  - Impact Analysis, n.d. 1982 (Box 13)
  - Industrial Development Authority Application 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Information and Tickets Area 1985 (Box 13)
  - Inspection Services 1984 (Box 13)
  - Internal Plan 1983 (Box 13)
  - Land Assembly 1984 (Box 13)
  - Land Assembly-Correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Lease Agreement, Miscellaneous Correspondence [Financial Contributions] 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Leasing-Minority Recruitment Plan, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Legal Documents 1982-1984 (Box 13)
  - Letters of Intent, n.d. 1981-1983 (Box 13)
  - Letters of Intent-Correspondenc, Notes, News clipping 1983 (Box 13)
  - Marcellus, Wright, Cox, and Smith 1983 (Box 13)
  - Marcellus, Wright, Cox, and Smith-Construction Cost 1983 (Box 13)
  - Marketplace Parking Garage 1984 (Box 13)
  - McGaughy, Marshall and McMillan 1983 (Box 13)
  - McGuire, Woods, and Battle 1983-1985 (Box 13)
  - Media-Negative TV Reporting [Channel Six, Richmond] 1984 (Box 13)
  - Miller and Rhoads, Allied Stores-Correspondence, Notes, Architectural Drawings 1984 (Box 13)
  - Miller and Rhoads-Contribution 1984 (Box 13)
  - Minority Business 1983 (Box 13)
  - Minority Business and Tenant Opportunity 1984 (Box 13)
  - Minority Business and Tenant Program 1984 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Notes, and Reports, n.d. 1984-1986 (Box 13)
  - Moore, T. Justin-Correspondence 1984 (Box 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1983 (Box 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1956-1984 (Box 13)
  - Opening Festivities 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - Ordinances 1984 (Box 13)
  - Partnerships 1984 (Box 14)
  - Plan for Persons with Disablities 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Planning, Feasibility Study, Executive Director Search 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Potential Architechts 1983 (Box 14)
  - Pre-Constructions 1984 (Box 114)
  - Predevelopment Activities 1984 (Box 14)
  - Predevlopment Agreement, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Predevelopment Agreements 1984 (Box 14)
  - Pre-Development Agreement (EDC)-Enterprise Development Company 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Preservation/Urban Design Inc. 1983 (Box 14)
  - Press Releases April 8, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Press Releases, Special Events, Advertising 1986 (Box 14)
  - Prospective Planning and Architectural Consultants 1983 (Box 14)
  - Prospective Tenant Lists 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Prospects-A.J. Gourmet Ice Cream 1984 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Construction/Management (1 of 3) 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Construction/Management (2 of 3) 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Construction/Management (3 of 3) 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Resolutions 1983 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Suppliers/Contractors (1 of 2) 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Suppliers/Contractors (2 of 2) 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Tenants, n.d. 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Proposed Names for Marketplace 1983 (Box 14)
  - Project One Design Coordination 1984 (Box 14)
  - Public Works 1984 (Box 14)
  - Refinancing Options, Correspondence, Budgets, n.d. 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Request for Copies of Tansparancies 1984 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Festival marketplace, Inc.-Correspondence 1983-1987 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Redevelopment Housing Authority-Contribution to Marketplace 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Redevelopment Housing Authority-Loan Documents 1984 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Renaissance-Operating Plan/Budget 1985 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Renaissance-Board of Director's-Correspondence, Minutes 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Richmond Renaissance-Contributions to the Sixth Street Marketplace 1984 (Box 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Articles on Richmond Renaissance and Richmond 1984 (Box 15)
  - Rountrey and Associates-Appraisal of Sixth Street Marketplace 1984 (Box 15)
  - Security 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Signing/Closing 1985 (Box 15)
  - Sixth Street Action Committee 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Sixth Street Action Committee-Correspondence, Reports, n.d. 1983 (Box 15)
  - Sixth Street Festivals, n.d. 1983 (Box 15)
  - Sixth Street Marketing Task Force 1986 (Box 15)
  - Sixth Street Press Conference November 9, 1983 (Box 15)
  - South Street Structure 1983 (Box 15)
  - Status Reports and Checklists 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Strategy Proposals, n.d. (Box 15)
  - Subsoils 1983 (Box 15)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, n.d. 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Thalhimers-Correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Thalhimers-Design Planning-Correspondence, Notes, Drawings 1984 (Box 15)
  - Thalhimers-Meetings 1984 (Box 15)
  - Thalhimers-Participation 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Time Schedules 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Touche Ross and Co.-Report on Examination of Financial Statements of Federal Grant Revenues and Expenditures-Correspondence, n.d. 1983-1985 (Box 15)
  - Transportation 1983 (Box 15)
  - Urban Development Action Grant 1983 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant 1983-1985 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant 1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant 1985 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant-Application leverage ratio 1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant-Correspondence, contract, n.d. 1984 (Box 16)
  - Correspondence, notes 1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant-Correspondence, reports 1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant-Grant Agreement and Implementation (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant-Grant Agreements (1 of 2) 1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant-Grant Agreements (2 of 2) 1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant-Sixth Street Marketplace-Correspondence, Notes 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant Forms-Correspondence, notes, n.d. 1984 (Box 16)
  - Urban Development Action Grant and Funding 1984 (Box 16)
  - Virginia Center for the Performing Arts 1984 (Box 16)
  - Virginia Center for the Performing Arts-Correspondence 1984 (Box 16)
  - Wallace, Roberts, and Todd-Correspondence, Notes 1984 (Box 16)
  - Wallace, Roberts, and Todd-Invoices 1984 (Box 16)
  - Wheat, First Securities, Inc. 1984 (Box 16)
  - Whiting-Turner Contracting Co.-Correspondence, Notes 1984 (Box 16)
  - Working Group-City and Richmond Renaissance (check list) May 16, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Working Group Status Reports 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Zuchelli, Hunter and Associates 1983 (Box 16)
  - Zuchelli, Hunter Report and Analysis, n.d. 1983 (Box 16)
- Series IV--General Office Files and Correspondence, n.d. 1982-1989
  - Art District, n.d. 1982, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Broad Street Task Force 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - Brochure- Keep the James Off the Rocks-notes, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Central Richmond Association Parking Shuttle, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Commonwealth Mailing Systems 1983-1984 (Box 17)
  - Downtown Parking and Transportation 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Downtown Parking-Christmas 1984 (Box 17)
  - Gateway Project, n.d. 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Richmond Renaissance Brochures, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Parking-Includes Project 1 Area Parking Study; Miscellaneous Correspondence, Reports 1985 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Accounting Practices 1983 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Agreement June 23, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Annual Reports 1984-1989 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Articles and By-Laws 1983 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Board of Directors 1983-1987 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Closing Attorney Selection 1983 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Liability Policy # 949-2310 1983-1984 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Loan Committee Meeting Agendas 1983-1985 (Box 17)
  - Richmond Renaissance Development Corporation-Loan Committee-Operations Guide 1983 (Box 17)
  - SADTKO, n.d. 1983 (Box 17)
  - Second Street-Reports, including 2nd Street Business District reports 1983-1984 (Box 17)
  - Shockoe Slip; Guidelines for Development-UVA School fo Architecture-Draft January 24, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Small Business Administration-Certified Development Company Application 1983 (Box 17)
  - Small Business Administration 503 Loans Down the Road 1984 (Box 17)
  - SOT II, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Stadium 1983 (Box 17)
  - West End Machine Welding 1984 (Box 17)
- Series V--Miscellaneous Reports and Publications, n.d. 1969-1995
  - Bank CDC's: Financing Economic Development April 22, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Beyond Linkage, Tremont Plaza Hotel, Baltimore, Maryland May 19, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Briefing Seminars for State and Local Government officials on the Tax Reform Act of 1986-Sponsored by National League of Cities; Government Finance Officers Association (Box 18)
  - Center City Enviroment and Transportation: Local Government Solutions-U.S. Department of Transportation (Box 18)
  - City of Richmond, Virginia 1986-1987 Annual Report 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Community Redevelopmnent Agency of the City of Los Angeles, California, Official Statement 1985, Redevelopment Project Tax Allocation bonds, Series E (Box 18)
  - Community Redevelopmnent Agency of the City of Los Angeles, California, Official Statement 1985, Redevelopment Project Tax Allocation bonds, Series F (Box 18)
  - Downtown Planning-Survey Results, December 1989, International Downtown Association 1989 (Box 18)
  - EDAW Report December 22, 1988 (Box 18)
  - EDAW brochure (Box 18)
  - Face Rehabilitation of A.T. Holt Building: First and Poplar Street Macon Georgia 1986 (Box 18)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government Bulletin-Spring/Summer, Winter 1989, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Journal of Real Estate Development 1985-1990 (Box 18)
  - Kleos 1990 (Box 18)
  - Municipal Leasing: A Primer-Joseph C. Daley, October 1983 (Box 18)
  - Planning, Development, and Marketing Tools for the 1990s-International Downtown Association 1990 (Box 18)
  - Planning Programming Budgeting for City State County Objectives-State Local Finances (Box 18)
  - Profile 1989-A State of the City Report-Richmond, Virginia 1989 (Box 18)
  - Proposal From Richmond, A Living Classic, Prepared for Site Selection Committee, International Downtown Association 1990 (Box 18)
  - Regional Public Transportation Services Study, Preparted for the Richmond Area Metropolitan Transportation Planning Organization February 1988 (Box 18)
  - Retail Market Analysis, Downtown Richmond, Richmond, Virginia 1990 (Box 18)
  - Richmond Neighborhood Team (Box 19)
  - Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority-Miscellaneous Reports and Publications 1980s (Box 19)
  - Second Street Business District-Building Survey-n.d. [Includes Photographs] (Box 19)
  - Small Business Participation in the Economic Development of Depressed Urban Sites: Implications for Enterprise Nones and Other Incentive Policies Prepared for the U.S Small Business Administration November 1983 (Box 19)
  - Strategies for Cities and Counties: A Strategic Planning-Public Technology Inc. 1980s (Box 19)
  - Virginia Housing Directory 1991 (Box 19)
  - Vision for Downtown in the 1990s: A Mid-Winter Meeting, February 1991 (Box 19)
  - Who's Who in Metro Richmond Business 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Working Together: A Guide to Federal and State Resources for Rural Economic Development-Southwestern Bell Telephones 1988 (Box 19)
- Series VI-Photographs, Slides, Video and Audio Tapes, n.d. 1984-1990
  - Audio Cassesttes- Do the Town Theme Music (Box 20)
  - Audio Cassesttes-Downtown Richmond-Generic Version [2 copies] (Box 20)
  - Audio Cassesttes-James River (Unpulsed)/(Pulsed) (Box 20)
  - Keeping Up Appearances-Inaudible pulsed (Box 20)
  - Audio Cassesttes-Richmond Renaissance Jackson to the James[2 copies] (Box 20)
  - Audio Cassesttes-Richmond Renaissance Slide Show November 4, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Audio Cassesttes-(Cassette with no label) (Box 20)
  - Slides-Album 1-Slides of Broad St. (Box 20)
  - Slides-Album 2-Downtown Core (Box 20)
  - Slides-Album 3-Southwest Corridor (Box 20)
  - Slides-Album 4-Metro Richmond-General (Box 4)
  - Slides-Album 5-North Core (Box 20)
  - Slides-Album 6-Misc. Richmond (Box 20)
  - Video Cassette Tape- Valentine Museum: Two Street, Main Street Productions (Box 20)
  - Slides-Album 7-Jackson Ward (Box 21)
  - Slides-Album 8-Sixth Street Marketplace (Box 21)
    Album originally contained some photographs which were removed and placed in with other PR photographs, Box 9
  - Slides-Album 9-Richmond Renaissance: Projects, Plans, Presentations, Special Events (Box 21)
  - Slides-Album 10-Jackson Ward I (Box 21)
  - Downtown Richmond-Map-Richmond Department of Planning and Community Development 1984 (Box 22)
  - Folder 1-Computer Disks [Jackson Ward, Vision 2000 - Disk 1; Jackson Ward, Vision 2000 - Disk 2; Labels: Richmond Renaissance. The contents of all three disks were printed by SCA in July 1996 and are found in Series I--Jackson Ward] (Box 22)
  - Folder 2-Markup drafts for Renaissance Projects Report (Box 22)
  - Negatives-Trolley, Sixth Street Marketplace, Misc. (Box 22)
  - Photographs-Broad/Grace/2nd Street Conservation Ordinance 1991 (Box 22)
  - Photographs-Coaxum, Pamela (Box 22)
  - Photographs-Jackson Center 1991 (Box 22)
  - Lambert, Sen. Benjamin (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous, including Clarence L. Townes, Jr. at different events (Box 22)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace-Planning, Ground breaking, Opening (Box 22)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace-Proposed Perspectives, Models and Drawings (Box 22)
  - 200-202 E. Broad Street 1991 (Box 22)
  - 213 Clay Street 1991 (Box 22)
  - 516 N. 2nd Street 1991 (Box 22)
  - 526 N. 2nd Street 1991 (Box 22)
  - Brickwall Photographs, Four Slides, Negatives-includes documentation of where along the canal walk photographs were taken. (Box 22)
  - Press Package-Downtown Richmond, Inc. Press Package-includes Do the Town audio cassette, news releases, and other promotional material-includes business Card of Lucy B (Box 22)
  - Meade, Downtown Richmond, Inc.'s Director of Marketing (Box 22)
  - Richmond Redevelopment Housing Authority Program Areas-Map, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Slide Carousel Labeled Riverfront (Box 22)
  - Small Archival Box containing miscellaneous slides (Box 22)
- Series VII: Richmond Renaissance Inventory 1997
  - Virginia Division of Tourism 1992-1994 (Box A1)
  - Virginia Historical Society (Box A1)
  - Virginia Hospitality and Travel Assoc. 1994 (Box A1)
  - Worlds Fair: Eastern Virginia 1994 (Box A1)
  - City: Econ. Development Office; June 1994 (Box A1)
  - City: Council; Aug 1994 (Box A1)
  - City Manager; April 1994 (Box A1)
  - Chapel Isle (Box A1)
  - Chimborazo (photo) (Box A1)
  - Confederate Navy Yard 1993 (Box A1)
  - Fall of Richmond Fire 1993 (Box A1)
  - Gabriel/Patrick Henry 1991 (Box A1)
  - Sports Hall of Fame 1991-1993 (Box A1)
  - St. John's (photo) (Box A1)
  - Trigg 1992 (Box A1)
  - Visitor Center 1991 (Box A1)
  - Econ. Impact: Tourism (see also Va. Div. of Tourism) 1992-1994 (Box A1)
  - Chadbourne 1988-1993 (Box A1)
  - Clarion Association 1993-1994 (Box A1)
  - Lawless 1993 (Box A1)
  - Riva 1993 (Box A1)
  - Food Industry 1993 (Box A1)
  - Hotel Industry 1994 (Box A1)
  - Transportation Industry 1994 (Box A1)
  - TDA-Transport 1993 (Box A1)
  - ULT 1991 (Box A1)
  - Va. Employment Commission 1993-1994 (Box A1)
  - Budget: Phase I 1993-1994 (Box A1)
  - Riverboat Gaming 1994 (Box A1)
  - Kleos 1994 (Box A1)
  - Reading 1994 (Box A1)
  - Virginia Business; Vol. 4, no. 3; Vol.9, no. 2; Vol. 9, no. 8; Vol 9 no. 6 (Box A1)
  - Ethyl Corp. Annual Report 1993 (Box A1)
  - Metro Richmond 1994 (Box 1)
  - Owens and Minor, Inc. Annual Report 1993 (Box A1)
  - Natural Lands Trus-Randall Arendt 1994 (Box A1)
  - Cadmus Communications Annual Report 1993 (Box A1)
  - International Festival Association 1994 (Box A1)
  - The City as a Themed Destination; Phase I; Feasibility 1993 (Box A1)
  - Pacific Mutual Annual Report 1990 (Box A1)